p1=[{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"bd","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"logorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"žati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"cr","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tača","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"čov","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"te","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ca","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"litelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"telina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tinjstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"dvos","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gluhon","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gluhosl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gn","osnova2":"zdo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"gor","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"grabl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"gr","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"grobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"gus","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"in","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kasn","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kl","osnova2":"šta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kol","osnova2":"vka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"vstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"lica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"gati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ska","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pota","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"stve","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"šnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"šati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"mišl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"riti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sec","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"štaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"napr","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"can","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"catelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"čaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"lja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"nevr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"mački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"obav","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"siti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"oc","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"nuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ogr","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"om","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"oruž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"osm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ozl","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"nt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"smarica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ščanik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pob","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"podr","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"poned","osnova2":"ljak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prad","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"predsobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"stiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"štati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"laz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"nos","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"voz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"primor","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"tka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prizeml","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"priznan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"raskriž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"redosl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"č","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"dak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"rubl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sav","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"čanj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"cište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ćati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"kira","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"menka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"titi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ver","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"veroistok","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verozapad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"gović","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"spr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"stan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"stol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"susn","osnova2":"žica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tliti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tiljka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tionik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"šted","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"šut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"T","osnova2":"lovo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"rati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"stenina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"toplom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"tros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ugl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"uman","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"upotr","osnova2":"biti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vesel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vis","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"čnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ronauk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučitelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"šalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"štica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ština","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"tar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"trovit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"verica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vrt","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zal","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zapov","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zav","osnova2":"sa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zd","osnova2":"la","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"z","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zda","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"znica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"zo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"živ","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
]

p2=[{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"cvjeta","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aroban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"as","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asopis","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"empres","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešalj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeset","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokratnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokut","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"inele","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itanka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"izma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uditi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"udo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrst","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"druk","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dvoto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ivan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kle","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"klju","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kornja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kota","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kov","osnova2":"eg","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"krma","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lopo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ljulja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"masla","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mladun","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mom","osnova2":"ad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naslonja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"natika","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"natje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"novorođen","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"njema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uh","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ogrta","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pješ","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"je","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pokaziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pokriva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"presko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"raj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"savija","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"strunja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tratin","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"ionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"usisava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uspinja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zajedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zavi","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ži","osnova2":"ara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"bi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"Boži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"boži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"up","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"došaš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"goš","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"izi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"kozli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"k%ur%uš","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"eha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"uhica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"miši","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"nesre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pam","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"plu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"polno","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pove","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ražnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"si","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"snjegovi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"spava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"srnda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"staja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"stolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"svu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"štapi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"trudno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"uš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vrti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"zada","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
]

p3=[{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"deter","osnova2":"ent","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"emper","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eparac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ungla","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"ho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"pan","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"benik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"kra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"novoro","osnova2":"enče","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"oru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"poga","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"poro","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"strojovo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"tvr","osnova2":"ava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"uspore","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
]